♪ ♪
Now, here's the
heart of it, Ben.
If I leave my Rudy
Vallée records
to my sweet niece Charlene,
then I've got to leave
my Nelson Eddy records
to her whiny sister.
Hmm.
Those records
are priceless, Ben.
Yeah.
You're not taking notes.
It's like I told you.
There are wills you
can make out yourself
where you don't have
to pay a person like me.
Well, you know what they say.
A man who does his own
will has a fool for a will maker.
That's not the saying. It's not?
No, it's:
"A man who defends himself
has a fool for a lawyer."
Mm, same thing.
I'll tell you what,
tell you what.
You make out a list and
I'll make sure it's legal.
Ben, you're a genius.
I'll be back with a list as
long as an encyclopedia.
Oh, Mr. Matlock.
Oh, please, you've
got to help me.
Mr. Matlock, my
name is Jennifer Holtz.
I'm a psychic.
I can see into the future.
Mr. Matlock, someone
is going to be murdered.
It's not me, is it?
What? It's not me.
No, you're too small.
Oh, good.
Now, don't you worry.
You come right with me
and have a seat right in there,
and everything's
going to be all right.
Cute chick, but two
sandwiches short of a picnic,
if you get my drift.
Mm-hmm.
Now, tell me, Miss Holtz,
what can we do to help you?
Well, I'm staying at
the Crown Regent Hotel
for the New World convention.
Oh, it's a gathering of
psychics and New Age people.
It happened in my hotel room.
Somebody was killed
in your hotel room?
No, no, that's where
I had the vision.
Oh, you must believe me.
I saw it all.
A man... a tall, muscular man...
Stabbed in the back
with a glass spear.
Holy cow.
Uh... let me, let me,
let me get this straight.
Um, nobody's been killed?
Within 48 hours,
this man will die,
and I will be accused
of the murder.
And I didn't do it.
Of course you didn't.
Well, no, she didn't because
a murder hasn't been committed.
What exactly is it that
you want, Miss Holtz?
I need a defense lawyer.
Well, you, you can't
be defended, uh,
for murder until a
murder's been committed.
I mean, somebody has to be dead.
That's the law.
You must help me,
please, Mr. Matlock.
Maybe we'd bett-better
get something straight.
I'm Mr. Matlock.
He's Mr. Calhoun.
I'm a retired businessman.
You can call me Ace.
You made a lot of money.
I've done pretty well.
And will continue to do so.
Really?
Where's Jennifer Holtz?
How would I know?
Cyril's gone and
booked her a radio spot,
and she's an hour late.
Well, perhaps in the future
she sees, there aren't any clocks.
Shh.
We'd like you WZF
listeners to know this is
the largest gathering
of psychics, healers,
trance channelers ever
assembled in your city,
and Jennifer Holtz
will appear daily.
I was a headline channeler
before Jennifer Holtz
knew her astral
projection from her karma.
Second billing is an insult to
my spiritual entity Ramutiki.
If Ramutiki survived
being beheaded in Babylon,
I think he'll survive
second billing.
Where do they get this garbage?
They make it up.
Ramutiki is predicting
an expanding economy,
worldwide prosperity.
Yes, there will be over
a hundred booths...
Crystals, tarot readings,
aura readings, astrology,
psychic healing, numerology,
every aspect of
New Age thinking.
Thank you, Mr. Fessman.
Your Ramutiki is
off his astral nut.
Saturn has gone into Capricorn;
Wall Street's
heading for a crash.
You're crazy.
Uranus is in Capricorn
in the tenth house.
The stock market will boom.
Ramutiki told you this?
I channeled him this
morning. Yeah, well,
he's coming through fuzzy.
Jennifer says
that... Jennifer again.
Predicting a depression?
Oh, shut up, Spaulding.
Has, uh, has anyone
seen Jennifer?
Marie.
Jennifer, where have you been?
Um, Jennifer, I could
use some advice.
Of course.
You look terrible.
Haven't eaten or
slept, have you?
Come on, we're
going to have lunch.
We'll be back in an hour.
Where are you going?
You've got radio spots,
you've got newspaper interviews.
Well, this is important.
Jennifer, you're the
best, and so beautiful.
Oh, Dick.
Why, how can you
be so cruel to her?
Marie.
Yeah, and then... then
she says... she says,
"In 48 hours, a
man will be killed
and I will be blamed
for the murder."
♪ Doo-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo. ♪
She was a nice
enough girl... attractive...
Just one of those dames that's,
you know, a bubble off plumb.
As long as she was there,
why didn't you ask her
to read your fortune?
No, no, no, no fortune.
I don't want to know
about the future.
I want it to be
a surprise. Well,
I just thought that you
might have asked her
if there was anybody
special in your future.
Oh, yeah, well...
Here comes Les.
Hey, Ben, you'll never guess.
Oh, hi, Les.
You know that high-tech
egg stock I told you about?
Oh, Julie and I were just
having a, a quiet dinner.
Well, go ahead, eat.
Anyway, there was
a two-for-one split,
and the stock went
right through the roof
and I made a bundle,
just like she said.
What are you talking about?
Jennifer Holtz.
She told me yesterday
I'd make a killing, and I did.
And now she says my
hair is going to grow back.
Oh, well, that's exciting.
Hi, Julie. Hi.
Boy, am I starved.
How did you find
out we were here?
Did Jennifer predict it?
No.
You think I'm some
sort of weirdo?
I called your answering
service and they told me.
Oh, hmm.
Can I have your pickle?
Dick?
Oh, my God!
No!
No... no!
Hold it!
I'm coming, I'm
coming, I'm coming.
I'm coming.
Hold your horses.
It happened, just as I saw it!
What happened, Miss Holtz?
The stabbing...
Just like my vision.
Dick Blake... he's, he's dead.
Stabbed in the back
with a crystal wand.
Who's Dick Blake?
He's the assistant
manager of the convention.
I found him in
the Crystal Suite.
Don't you see?
It's just as I predicted.
And now they're
going to accuse me.
Oh.
Wa-Was anybody else there?
Well... no, when
I first went in,
and... and then
someone came, and I...
I panicked and ran.
Oh. You ran from the
scene of the crime?
Oh, I didn't kill him.
Oh. Oh, you've got to help me.
Oh. Well, we've got
to go to the police.
Will you represent me?
Oh, I knew you would.
Oh, I don't know. I don't know.
Uh, ah, sit down
somewhere. But...
I've got to put on some pants
if I'm going into town.
Do you ever get the feeling
that people are-are...
are out to get you?
You're describing
paranoia, Mr. Matlock.
And I'm not crazy.
But you-you hear voices
and-and-and spirits.
Yes.
I hear my guides
and my teachers.
But not here.
Here.
Well, I don't... I
don't understand.
Ever since I was a child,
I... I had feelings.
Intuitions about
what would happen.
And then when I
learned to meditate,
I started to have visions.
For a while, I tried to deny it.
I didn't want people to
think that I was crazy.
So, I went to college,
got a real estate license.
But... selling flats wasn't...
I was put here to help
people, Mr. Matlock.
Do you understand?
Um...
I don't understand
about being psychic.
And I don't think
the prosecution will
understand, either.
I think he will understand
a-a witness seeing you
flee the scene of a murder
the day after you predicted it.
What were you doing in
the Crystal Room that night?
Dick asked me to
meet him at the office.
I was giving him
private readings.
He was in a very negative space.
He seemed... almost desperate.
When I got to the
office, he wasn't there,
but I noticed the door to
the Crystal Suite was open.
And that's where I found him.
Well, w-why did you run?
I mean, why didn't
you go for help?
When I found Dick,
the most horrifying
vision I've ever had
in my life came true
in front of my eyes.
I was afraid!
Mm.
I want my money!
Spaulding, I've got much
bigger things to worry about
than your paycheck.
You'll have to wait
for your money.
I don't have a cent.
Why don't you
channel up Ramutiki
and hit him up for a loan?
Uh, excuse us. We're
looking for Iris Vogel.
We're attorneys.
I'm Michelle Thomas,
this is Ben Matlock.
Uh, we're defending,
uh, Jennifer Holtz,
uh, for the murder
of, uh... Dick Blake.
Uh, uh, Dick Blake.
What do you mean?
Jennifer's been arrested?
Oh, this is a disaster.
Uh, well,
could we ask you
a few questions?
I'm sorry. I-I... I can't.
Uh, Cyril, just please
tell them anything
that they want to know.
Oh... Iris!
None of this surprises me.
Everyone knew Dick
and Jennifer were lovers.
He was a rat with women.
She was a jealous,
lovesick girl.
And Spaulding Kane
is a spiteful phony
who's thrilled to have
Jennifer out of the way.
Hmm. And, so, uh,
Jennifer, uh, Holtz
is the real thing, huh?
Certainly.
Even the best psychics
have a 75% accuracy rate.
But take a look at this
chart I did on Jennifer
for an article in Cosmic
Consciousness Journal.
Jennifer Holtz is 96% accurate.
Hmm.
How often does she
predict things, like, um,
it'll be hot in Atlanta in July?
You're a skeptic.
That's fine.
But believe it or not,
there is a new
consciousness coming.
And from the size of
this convention, a lot
of money.
That's what attracts
the frauds and the fakes.
This is Marie's showroom.
Huh.
She works with
very powerful crystals
used to induce channeling
and promote good health.
Oh. Yeah.
Promote good health, huh?
Good health.
Hmm.
Didn't do much for his, did it?
Huh.
Oh, he's facing out here.
That way... Hmm.
Boy, he could have donated
a lot of blood, couldn't he?
Yes.
Hmm. What time
did the coroner say?
Oh, about 9:00 p.m. About 9:00.
Murder weapon was a crystal
wand about 18 inches long.
Those there.
Marie designs those herself.
Nothing's missing.
Yeah.
Good health.
Uh, where would we
find Marie Willis now?
Oh, she's probably
up in her room.
She's upset about Jennifer,
but she took Dick's
death hard, too.
She loved him.
He treated her very badly.
But then, he treated
all women badly.
You didn't like him
very much, did you?
I hated him.
He was a self-serving,
muscle-bound hustler.
He was even taking
bribes from vendors
for better positions
in the convention hall.
Oh.
Well, the murder
took place about 9:00.
At 9:00, I was
having dinner with Iris
in the hotel dining room.
Sorry.
But all those we've talked to,
all of 'em sounded
like they wouldn't
mind killing, uh...
Dick Blake. Yeah.
Well, maybe Marie
will have a kind word
to say about him.
Yeah. Here.
Hmm.
I smell smoke.
Yeah, it's in here.
Hurry!
There may be a
fire in here. Fire.
A key. Key. Key.
Oh. Oh, there.
Come on. Come on.
I should know better.
Uh, well, yes, you're right.
Suicide's no answer.
Yes, it is.
But it's very bad karma.
Oh, well, whatever you say.
Uh, do you... do you feel like
answering a few questions?
I think so.
Okay. Uh... This crystal wand...
It's mine.
I design them.
Uh-huh.
W-Was it missing
from your display case?
I gave it to Dick a month ago.
As a birthday present.
Uh-huh.
Oh, what was he doing in
the Crystal Suite that night?
Had you arranged
to-to... to meet him there?
No.
I waited in my
room for him to call.
I waited all night.
You did?
Yes.
I would have done
anything for him.
He lied to me.
He cheated on me.
But I loved him.
Mr. Matlock... I
had... I had no choice.
You-You didn't kill him.
No.
He was my soul mate.
Uh... You say he cheated on you?
He was a womanizer.
Who-Who was he, uh, uh... with?
I never dared meditate on that.
I started working with crystals
because I'm a very good psychic.
But I... I can't bear
to tell people the bad things
that I see in their future,
or look at the bad things
that'll happen to me.
Please don't ask me to
meditate on that. Please.
I don't want to.
No. No, I... No, I wouldn't
ask you to meditate on that.
No.
Who-Who was the last,
uh, okay... woman
you saw him with?
Jennifer.
He said some very
sweet things to her.
He even kissed her.
For a moment... Mr. Matlock,
Jennifer's my best friend,
and she knew how
desperately I loved Dick.
How desperately I loved him.
She would never betray me.
She would never, never...
Good news from my spirit guides.
You're going to
prove me innocent.
Oh.
Well, I might as
well just go fishing
and let your spirit
guides take over.
Jennifer...
we have a dirt poor case,
and unless I can get
some hard, provable facts,
you're going to be
convicted of murder.
I don't know who's
trying to frame you,
but whoever it is is
doing a pretty good job.
But who would want to frame me?
I don't know.
Maybe Marie.
She was damn
jealous of her soul mate,
and he was coming on to you.
Oh, Marie wouldn't, couldn't.
But she's the best, most
honest person I know.
Besides, everyone,
including Marie,
knew that I had a reading
for Mrs. Murphy that night.
I cancelled it at
the very last minute.
Nobody knew I was meeting Dick.
So no one's framing me.
Hi, gang!
Oh. Hi, Les.
Hi, Ben.
Hi, Jennifer.
Well, I'm here for the
latest bulletin from beyond.
Mr. Calhoun, could we
talk in private... later?
Oh, I got no secrets from Ben.
We're buddies.
Besides, I want to
show the skeptic here
how you do your stuff.
I want you to remember
that... Cosmically speaking...
There are no accidents.
You've lived many lives
and will continue
to live many more.
You're going to tell me who
I'm going to be born as next,
so I can leave my
money to myself.
Uh, no.
The stock market's going down?
No.
I mean, yes, but you won't care.
Oh, Mr. Calhoun.
I'm obligated to tell you
what my spirit
guides have told me.
You won't live to
hear the verdict
of this trial.
Are you sure?
I mean, I know
your spirit guides
mean well, but...
uh, maybe they're talking
about another Les Calhoun.
Did they mention a ZIP code?
Uh... I don't want to die.
How's Marie?
She'll be okay.
Good.
I got some stuff on Dick Blake.
Yeah? Everything
from petty theft
to major cons to kiting checks.
No kidding.
I wonder why Iris hired him.
Maybe she didn't know.
And he had other talents.
Oh, yeah.
I've been hearing that.
Yeah. Yeah.
He was a bodybuilder.
Yeah, yeah.
He spent part of the
time building his body
and then the rest of it
chasing somebody else's.
Well, they say it's
good for the heart.
Yeah, I guess so.
I did some poking around.
Yeah? Look at this.
Room service receipts
from the week before the murder.
All signed by him?
Uh-huh.
Look at the room number: 1737.
Dick Blake was in room 247.
Oh.
Maybe you better
see who's in 1737.
I'll hang around out here.
Miss Vogel, you mind if I
ask you a few questions?
I'm very busy.
I understand.
You'd rather I
ask them in court?
Come in.
What was your
relationship to Dick Blake?
Strictly business.
He managed the
day-to-day business
of setting up the
convention for you?
Yes, he did...
and none too well.
Well, you couldn't have been
too unhappy with his work.
Uh, champagne and
chocolate mousse at 2:00 a.m.
Seems almost romantic.
Dick's idea of a coffee break.
That was the night
that we worked
on the final convention budget.
It took until dawn.
Saving expenses was
not his strong point.
Then, he wasn't...
living with you?
No.
No, Dick appealed to women
who needed to suffer for love.
I'm not one of them.
Thank you, Miss Vogel.
Oh, hi, Les.
Ben!
Ben, I feel awful.
How do I look?
You're not going to
die. But she said I was.
Well, she could
be wrong. Well...
But you know what?
I believe your
hair is growing in.
Really? Uh-huh.
Yeah.
Ben.
He wasn't living here,
and none of his
things are in his room.
You'd think a guy who
was working out all the time
and chasing women
would want to take a shower.
Yeah.
Hey, who's the one person
would do anything
Dick Blake said
without asking questions?
Yeah.
Call Marie.
Okay, she said to
look in the closet.
Uh-huh.
Oh, here, here, here, here.
Yeah, here's...
here's Dicky's bag.
Poor Marie. Yeah, well,
like you say, love is blind.
Pay dirt.
Huh.
And everything he needed
to leave town in a hurry.
Yeah.
There must be thousands.
I think maybe we
better call the police.
The state calls
Mr. Benjamin Matlock.
Uh, Your Honor,
I trust that my learned
colleague knows
that an attorney
cannot be compelled
to divulge privileged
information.
I do not wish
privileged information,
Your Honor, but if
my learned colleague
is still unwilling to testify,
I'm sure we can
corroborate the information
from another witness.
Mr. Matlock, do you
recall where you were
and what you were doing
the night of the murder?
I was having dinner with
you at Ray Templin's bar.
And do you recall
our conversation
about a young woman
who made a certain prediction?
Yes, I do.
A prediction... and I quote...
"within 48 hours, a
man would be murdered,
stabbed in the back with
a glass spear"... unquote.
Now, Mr. Matlock, wasn't
that prediction made
a day before the murder?
Uh, Your Honor, I object.
Madam Prosecutor and I
were talking in a restaurant,
and my testimony
should be stricken
as hearsay and irrelevant.
Objection overruled.
Answer the question.
Yes.
Mr. Matlock,
do you agree that
this crystal wand,
which is the murder weapon,
might be described
as a glass spear?
I guess it might.
Uh-huh.
Now, Mr. Matlock,
isn't it true that the person
who made that
extraordinary prediction
is your client,
the defendant, Jennifer Holtz?
Yes.
I have just one more question.
Do you think your client
can predict the future?
Objection.
This calls for a conclusion
on the part of the witness.
I withdraw the question.
Miss Vogel, this key ring,
which you have identified
as belonging to the
victim, Mr. Blake,
contains keys to all
of the hotel suites,
does it not?
All of the suites that we
rented for our convention, yes.
Dick... Mr. Blake... Was
my assistant manager.
So, Mr. Blake could have entered
any of the hotel suites to
meet anybody at any time,
day or night?
Yes, of course.
Do you know who he
arranged to meet that night?
No.
He had his own life.
Did Mr. Blake ever
describe to you
his relationship
with the defendant,
Jennifer Holtz?
Yes.
He told me that Jennifer
was crazy about him,
called him night and day.
I wasn't surprised.
Dick seemed to attract
young, foolish girls.
Object.
Move to strike.
Strike the last remark.
No further questions.
Considering the hour,
I'm going to recess
until 9:00 a.m.
tomorrow morning.
Uh... Ben?
Uh, uh... uh, just curious.
How much longer do
you think this trial will last?
Well...
I think it will last
long enough that...
when you die, you'll
have a full head of hair.
I don't see what the point is.
I already told the
police what I saw.
That woman ran out of here
like demons were after her.
Nothing's been touched.
Court order.
Court order... yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, he must have
been facing this way,
'cause that's the way he fell.
Yeah.
Marie said that, uh,
she gave him that wand.
And... maybe he brought
it up here with him?
Why would he bring the
murder weapon with him?
Well, surely, he
didn't bring it with him
'cause he thought
somebody would kill him.
Maybe he... maybe
he was going to sell it.
Here, you take the wand.
Slip up behind me.
Okay. See if you can kill me.
Okay. No, no, no, no.
Not unless he was asleep.
He would have seen his killer.
I can see you.
That's strange.
Just... Doesn't make any sense.
I'm dogged.
Miss Willis, uh, how... how long
have you known Jennifer Holtz?
About seven years. And-and
how would you describe
your relationship?
We're friends.
And you would never
do anything to hurt her,
would you?
Never.
And she would never
do anything to hurt you.
No, she wouldn't.
I... I have a friend like that.
His name is Lee Greenway.
We've been friends for...
oh, years and years and years.
We grew up together,
and we never...
never had a harsh
word between us.
We never...
never got mad and threw
rocks at one another,
you know, the way boys will do.
We were from the
country, I'm proud to say.
And there was a
girl that Lee liked.
Beautiful girl.
She was tall, had
long black hair.
And when Lee would see her,
he had a little
poem he liked to say.
He'd say, "If I'd
a-seed you a-coming,
"I'd have knowed what to do.
"I'd a-ris'
both arms and a-wove at you."
And she would laugh.
And after while...
I started to say it...
'cause I liked her myself.
And Lee never got mad at me,
because we were friends.
And so, I think I understand
your friendship with Jennifer.
You're like... two
halves of a coin.
That's exactly the way we are.
We're... twin souls
through many lives.
Yeah.
Were you aware or...
or.. or were you ever suspicious
of a relationship between
Jennifer and Dick Blake?
Jennifer was counseling Dick.
I see... I see.
Even though... he
called and begged her
to meet him secretly
late that night?
That was for counseling
and nothing more?
That's right.
I would've known if
it was anything else.
How would you have known?
Jennifer would've told me.
Even though she knew
how jealous you were of him?
Yes.
Jennifer told me everything.
You were that close?
Yes.
I believe you are.
And I believe that if
Jennifer had a vision,
a vision... as
important... as death...
Murder death...
if she told anyone,
she would've told you.
And I believe she
told you of her vision.
And then when Dick
Blake was killed...
you were terrified,
that Jennifer had done it.
And Jennifer knowing
of your jealousy
was very frightened,
that you had done it.
You have been
protecting each other.
Jennifer... did tell you...
every detail of her
prediction, didn't she?
Yes.
Now... this question
is very important
and you must answer
it truthfully, at all costs.
You did tell someone else
about Jennifer's
prediction, didn't you?
Yes.
Mr. Henning, Miss
Willis did tell you
about Jennifer's
prediction, didn't she?
Yes.
And I was convinced
it would come true.
I've been observing
Jennifer for a long time.
And I believe her
powers are extraordinary.
Now, uh, on the
night of the murder,
you were having
dinner with Miss Vogel.
In fact, you used to have dinner
with Miss Vogel all the time.
Yes, I did.
Because there was a relationship
that ended around the first
of the year.
That's right.
Now, as I said earlier,
we have a witness
who saw Miss Vogel leave
the restaurant before 9:00.
That same witness saw you
leave the restaurant
before 9:00.
Where did you go?
To my room.
Your Honor,
the witness is not on
trial here. Uh, Your Honor,
may I just continue with this?
Proceed.
Thank you.
So you went to your room.
Uh, did anyone visit you?
No.
So you were there all night?
Yes. Alone?
Yes!
Let the record state
that I'm showing the
witness State's Exhibit five.
The scene of the murder...
Better known to you
as the Crystal Suite.
Now, as you can see,
the victim's body
is facing this way.
Facing the mirror.
Now, how do you suppose
someone snuck up behind him
and stabbed without
being seen in the mirror.
I haven't the faintest idea.
No? I mean, seems to me
a man the size of Dick Blake
would've seen somebody
coming up to stab him,
and put up a fight.
One would think so.
Yeah, one would.
So...
it brought to my mind
another possibility.
Maybe...
maybe Dick Blake wasn't
killed in the Crystal Suite.
Maybe he was killed
somewhere else,
and then his body was moved.
What do you think?
I suppose that's possible.
Count on it.
Count on it, Mr. Henning.
I'm not psychic.
I can't talk to the spirits.
And even I know Dick Blake
was killed in your room.
Objection!
Mr. Matlock, unless
you have some basis
and proof, you'll
have to drop this
immediately. I believe
I have it, Your Honor.
Very well.
Now-now-now... now
just-just... Just listen to this.
See what you think.
You stabbed Dick Blake
with this crystal wand.
And he fell on the rug
in your room, bleeding heavily.
And you drug Dick Blake...
and the rug across the hall
to the Crystal Suite.
Where the body was found
just like Jennifer predicted.
Then you brought the
rug from the Crystal Suite
to your room.
That's what caught ya.
See, you thought
that all the rugs
in all the suites,
in all the rooms
were all alike.
But they're not. Thank you.
This is the rug from
the Crystal Suite.
This rug...
was impounded by
the police last night,
for evidence from your room.
Now, on the surface
these rugs look identical.
And they are except...
if you turn underneath
there's an inventory number
from the hotel that
matches the room
the rug goes in.
This is the rug from
the Crystal Suite.
The one with the blood.
The one...
Dick Blake fell on
after he was stabbed.
And the number
on the rug is 122.
Mr. Henning, what's
your room number?
What's your room number?
122.
The rug the police impounded...
has the number 123.
That's the number...
of the Crystal room.
And it came out of your room.
You switched them, didn't you?
Yes!
But I never intended that...
Jennifer would be
accused of Blake's murder.
I believe you.
And that's-that's what threw me.
You never tried
to frame Jennifer.
You thought she
had a perfect alibi.
She had a reading that night...
with Mrs. Murphy.
How could you know
she had canceled that reading
to meet with Dick Blake.
You would never do
anything to harm her,
would you? Of course not.
Jennifer is a
light in the world.
She's the most special
person I've ever known.
She's gifted beyond Nostradamus,
beyond Edgar Cayce, beyond...
Dick Blake wanted to use her...
Use her as a woman
for his pleasure,
and as a psychic for his profit.
He was a carnal man who
abused the spiritual gifts of others.
He mocked everything
the New Age stands for.
Dick Blake knew you
didn't like him, didn't he?
I made no secret of it.
Why'd he come to your room?
Greed!
His greed like his
ego had no limits.
He wanted to sell me the
crystal wand Marie gave him
and other valuable
crystals I'm certain he stole.
He brought the weapon with him.
You see, it was meant to be.
Oh, so, so you killed him...
and moved his body,
so it would look like
Jennifer's prediction
had come true.
The prediction did come true.
I was only the means.
I was destined
to kill Dick Blake
just as Jennifer was
destined to reveal it.
I knew the moment Marie told me,
that vision was meant for me.
Your Honor... I move to dismiss.
Does prosecution
have any objection?
None, Your Honor.
Motion is granted.
Miss Holtz, you're free to go.
This court is adjourned.
You'll be blessed with
long life and good health.
But what about me?
Les, the case was dismissed.
There was no verdict.
There was no jury
to give a verdict.
There never will be.
Then I'm gonna live!
www.tvsubtitles.net